We're here with two actors,
Namkoong Min and Kim Dae-myung,
deeply adored by many viewers.
One of our own chefs
was in a scene with Dae-myung
-and showed off his master acting skills.
-They acted?
-Someone acted?
-Really?
-Master skills?
-Who was it?
Chef Sam and I
were in the music video "THINK OF YOU"
by Young-jun of Brown Eyed Soul.
SAM KIM, AN ACTOR?
I was the owner of a tofu restaurant,
and he played a regular customer there.
-The customer?
-You were the customer?
You acted as the customer?
Isn't it supposed to be
the other way around?
We got our hands on that music video.
WE GOT THE MUSIC VIDEO
This is "THINK OF YOU" by Young-jun.
-No way.
-Let's watch it.
He was in it with Dae-myung.
See? There he is.
Tofu delivery.
Yes, it was tofu.
FELL IN LOVE WITH THE DELIVERY WOMAN
She was there to deliver tofu?
He wants to see her again.
It's Sam!
SAM KIM, A REGULAR CUSTOMER
Who does that to order more rice?
-Oh, no.
-Is he having bean rice?
MORE TOFU, NOT RICE
DOING HIS BEST TO SHOW A DUMBFOUNDED FACE
EVERYTHING IS TOFU
They're all tofu dishes.
That guy keeps coming back.
He is a regular there.
SAM SHOWED HIS MASTER SKILLS AS AN ACTOR
IN THE SAME SCENE WITH DAE-MYUNG
It was a prop,
so it probably tasted bad too.
BLUSH
-That was fun.
-He wasn't all that awkward.
-I can see now that I was quite talented.
-Talented in what?
YOU'RE RIGHT
Did you two meet
for the first time back then?
-Yes.
-It was the first time.
What was his first impression?
There are many actors
who are intimidatingly charismatic, right?
But he seemed more like my kind--
No, he isn't.
On the other hand, there are chefs
who are flashy and loud, aren't there?
THE FLASHY GUY
He's flashy.
-So he's more like you than Hyun-suk?
-That's it.
He seemed like the calmer type.
He's finally using his canine
to chew me out.
-He's starting to attack Hyun-suk.
-He's finally chewing out.
So he thinks Dae-myung is like him.
We actually received a tip
regarding Dae-myung.
He's famous as a foodie
in the entertainment business.
Also, he creates foodie content
under his own name,
titled Food, Vibe, Dae-myung.
How did that begin?
-FVD.
-When I meet
with writers or friends
that I'm close to,
we never drink a lot of soju
in just one place.
We have a beer somewhere,
then walk for about a kilometer
and have a drink of soju.
So I end up hopping
seven or eight times a day.
ALWAYS RESTAURANT-HOPS 7 TO 8 TIMES
It's like going on a day trip.
You go anywhere that catches your eye?
What's this about?
Your greatest rival is sitting right here?
Your greatest rival is here?
-Who's your rival?
-There is someone
-I've noticed recently…
-I think I know.
-…as a YouTuber.
-Huh?
-Who is it?
-It is
-Chef Nam-no.
-Yoon Nam-no!
He's been eating so much lately.
I watched him and realized
he and I are quite alike.
-We'd hit it off.
-Really?
You can tell whether a food show
is scripted or not, right?
Right. You can tell.
I can tell when it's genuine,
and you actually disclosed your favorites.
I only introduce places I've been to.
ME TOO!
And I also hop six, seven times.
Six, seven times?
I like to eat lightly
in many different places
-for over six to seven hours.
-I see.
That's not for me.
HAS A CLEAR PREFERENCE
You stick to one place.
-I like to just stay in one place forever.
-Yes, just staying put.
-It's too much of a hassle.
-Right? Why would you do that?
-Everything's there already.
-It's already so cozy.
-Just…
-In one place forever.
Min, do you like
looking for good restaurants?
I often make reservations through an app,
and I also enjoy finding
and dining at new joints.
Do you make reservations yourself
on the phone?
No, these days, there's an app.
-Who makes calls these days?
-Go on the internet. Please.
-Who makes calls?
-Go online for once.
Even I use apps.
"Hi, I'm Kim Sung-ju.
Can I make a reservation?"
-"Who are you?"
-Wait.
-I don't really use apps.
-Do you make calls?
-I do.
-What do you say?
-I ask if they have a spot.
-"Hi, you've reached Chef & My Fridge."
They'd ask for the caller,
-and I say, "Kim Sung-ju."
-Yes.
If they go, "Wait, that Kim Sung-ju?"
Then I reply, "Yes, that's me."
Some places then give me
a nice seat by the window.
He's like a senior.
He wants better treatment.
When I make a reservation somewhere new,
I do it under someone else's name.
The thing Hyun-suk gets attacked for
has come to me.
He should've said this.
-You need to talk less with age.
-All right.
A TIP FROM THE MOST TALKATIVE FRIEND
Anyway, sorry about that.
Here's the thing.
Let's say you went somewhere
and confirmed that the place is good,
so you now want to befriend the owner.
-That's important.
-I'm sure
-you have a secret to becoming friends.
-He must.
I'm quite introverted,
so I can never strike up a conversation.
If I like a place a lot,
I keep going for two to three years.
After some time,
I slowly initiate a conversation
by saying things like,
"Your restaurant looks so clean."
-That takes you two to three years?
-Yes.
-Not on the first day?
-No.
COMPLETE INTROVERT
It depends on the personality,
but some people go…
AMAZED
"This place is the best."
Who makes that sound
and does this these days?
We're no longer living
in the age of early 2000s infomercials!
BURST OUT IN A LAUGHTER!
Do you clap when you get your food?
KIM SUNG-JU, AGE 55
WOW!
Your food is so good. This is the best!
These days, people leave online reviews.
-They do?
-Yes.
MISSING THE OLD THINGS…
-Did you become acquainted with a few?
-Yes.
There's a place in Seochon
called A restaurant.
NAM-NO KNOWS THAT PLACE TOO
I've been going there for 15 years,
so the owner there
and I actually became friends.
We've traveled together,
and we know what's going on
with each other's families.
Our mothers are close too.
Can you share a few good places
you've been going to for years?
-Gosh.
-Yes?
I'm not sure
if I can share this on a show.
Or places with good vibes.
-Recently…
-Yes?
Recently?
I went to Yeonsinnae for a shoot.
Yeonsinnae.
There was a place that touched my heart
with an ordinary lunch.
Touched?
It was a Hamheung naengmyeon place.
Hamheung-style naengmyeon.
They only had four tables.
-Only four? It must be tiny.
-What? Just four?
Yes, only four tables,
and exactly three items on the menu.
Mul-naengmyeon, bibim-naengmyeon,
hoe-naengmyeon… Wait, one more.
Dumplings. Big-sized mandu.
A must at a naengmyeon place.
So we ordered two naengmyeon
and one mandu,
and most places like these
usually serve ready-made products, right?
Otherwise, it's not cost-effective.
INHALES
When I looked, their two workers
were wearing white uniforms
and white hats.
IMPRESSIVE UNIFORMS
Isn't it odd?
So I sat there and looked,
then noticed them
making noodles from scratch.
IN THE RESTAURANT?
And the mandu was this big.
So I cut it,
and the veggies inside spilled out.
I asked, "Do you make these here?"
And they said, "Every morning."
EVERYTHING IS HANDMADE
That was such a touching moment.
I'll look up that naengmyeon place.
It's in Yeonsinnae.
-Was it good?
-It was so delicious.
I should eat there too.
The word will go out.
It was the most delicious naengmyeon
I have had
in the last three to four years.
I'm interested.
What's the place called?
The name of the place
doesn't sound that good.
-What is it?
-It was N Generation in Yeonsinnae.
-N Generation?
JOTTING DOWN
-Not Girls' Generation?
It's like, "Right now, it's N Generation!"
I remember feeling deeply touched
after eating there.
-That's new.
-I see.
One of our chefs
once shared his favorite restaurant
and can no longer even make a visit.
Chef Jong-won?
Did this happen?
During an interview,
I was asked
to share my favorite restaurant.
And of course,
you want to share what you like, right?
-Yes.
-There was this bakery I loved,
so I shared it like it wasn't a big deal.
-Okay.
-But now that place has a waiting list.
It blew up.
-And there's a limit to what you can get.
-Right.
It became too famous,
so I haven't been able to go either.
You said it in a way
that'd make people want to go.
What did he say?
"I can hear the sound of a trumpet
from the sky when I eat this."
"If I could eat one thing before death,
I'd choose this."
What does it feel like
to hear trumpets in your ears?
Don't angels sound the trumpet
right before your death?
THE TASTE THAT LEADS YOU TO PARADISE
Who wouldn't go after hearing this?
He did the interview like it was
a Chef & My Fridge food review.
Don't you agree?
There's this place we both love
in Hannam-dong.
-Gamja-tang.
-That place.
I used to have team dinners there
when I started 30 years ago,
and it always had a table at any time.
Once it blew up,
people began to line up even at 1 a.m.
Then go at 2 a.m.
PRESENTING A SOLUTION
-Go at 2 a.m.
-You can go at 2 a.m.
The attack has returned to you.
You can always go at 2 a.m.
What's the problem?
Right! I could go at 2 a.m.!
Don't line up at 1 a.m.
You go to sleep way too early.
OLD ENOUGH TO SLEEP EARLY
AND WAKE UP EARLY…
Dae-myung, let's say
you went somewhere to eat,
but it wasn't as good as you thought.
-Right.
-After he ate there?
-It happens.
-It wasn't good.
-It happens too often.
-You had heard good things.
Then how do you feel?
I just don't have to show it.
But if the owner asks
and insists on getting feedback,
I try my best to find the best part,
even if I didn't like it.
AH-HA
For example, let's say the noodles
were too soggy at a kal-guksu place.
I go, "The food here will
definitely help me digest better."
That's scary.
If the noodles were undercooked,
I say, "There's a bite to it."
VEILED CRITICISM
"I love the texture."
I hope they understand what it means.
-He finds something.
-He's indirect about it.
-Listen closely to his reviews today.
-Yes, chefs.
I see. Between the lines?
Make sure you listen carefully.
The biggest foodie
in the entertainment business,
Dae-myung, brought his fridge,
and I wonder what he has inside.
-Do you use it alone?
-Yes.
I moved out while filming
Misaeng: Incomplete Life,
because I felt bad
about coming home so late.
So it's been a decade, about 12 years.
We may not see too many ingredients
because you're in a production now.
I clean it out when the production begins,
because I end up eating out
most of the time.
But toward the end of it,
I find time to fill it up again.
I keep filling it up and tell myself,
"The filming will end soon."
I fill it with what I want to eat.
I tell myself, "I'll make this
and eat it on the day it's over."
-I see.
-So I keep filling it up.
He's almost done filming the drama,
so I'm sure it's quite full now.
Let's look forward to what we'll find.
He's a foodie, so I'm looking forward
to seeing what he has.
Now, we present Dae-myung's fridge!
The foodie's fridge.
THEY'RE AMAZED?
-It's pretty full.
-That's not so bad.
-The foodie's fridge.
-The foodie!
PRESENTING DAE-MYUNG'S FRIDGE
COMPLETELY FULL
Look at this. He has all these sauces.
WHOA…
On the very top shelf,
there's one lone bread.
-Is this for when you feel peckish?
-That's…
-That's a really good one.
-The fact that it's in the fridge means
I drank the night before.
-Is that his hangover cure?
-Carbs.
Some people buy stuff when they're drunk.
On my way home
after drinking outside, for some reason,
I always stop at a convenience store.
A DRUNK PURCHASE
I always need that sweet bun.
So it wasn't just me.
I'm not sure if you know,
but that bread is great with makgeolli.
OH, MY
You're right.
Try a bite of that sweet bun
with makgeolli, rice wine.
You won't even remember where you are.
It goes really well with that rice aroma.
-Really? I didn't know that.
-Really?
Also with cheongju, refined rice wine.
-Why are you so excited?
-I'm serious.
-You're a lot like me.
-He's excited.
-He is.
-They're a good match.
Is this something you got delivered?
It's from my favorite bugeo-guk place
in Mugyo-dong.
In Hannam-dong?
-No, Mugyo-dong.
-Mugyo-dong.
Calm down! Keep your cool!
My mouth is suddenly watering.
I recently had a shoot nearby,
so I got it to go for after the shoot.
He kept it on stand-by.
Why do you like this place?
As a starter,
you get saeu-jeot, salted shrimp,
mixed with green onion and sesame oil.
-Salted shrimp?
-Yes, saeu-jeot.
And I always order a fried egg.
I love fried eggs.
I mix everything with my rice
before the soup is out
-and have a bite with closed eyes.
-He has a routine.
Then I'm already in paradise.
I KNOW WHAT THOSE TRUMPETS SOUND LIKE
He's my type.
Once I have a sip of the soup
with that rice, it's over.
-It must be that good.
-I wouldn't regret it even if I died.
-I want to swap seats with Jong-won.
-What else did you buy?
-Some herring roe jeotgal.
-This one?
It's from my friend's place, A restaurant.
Herring roe jeotgal.
-Herring roe.
-It's great when you have no appetite.
-That and some rice.
-You just need a spoon of that on rice
with a dash of sesame oil.
-Roasted seaweed.
-And roasted seaweed.
Or with gamtae, lattice-like seaweed.
-It's amazing.
-I have gamtae in my fridge!
-I knew it! Gamtae! You're a foodie!
-It's true.
I have gamtae.
IT'S THAT GOOD?
-Herring roe jeotgal with tofu.
-He has it.
I like to eat it with some tofu
and cucumber,
wrapped in gamtae.
ENGAGED
Then I end up where?
-Paradise.
He became eloquent
the moment we opened his fridge.
I FOUND MY MAN
He's so passionate about food,
much more than his acting career.
I'm so happy right now.
-What's this broth?
-That?
It's naengmyeon broth.
Naengmyeon broth.
-There's a DJ friend of mine, Tiger Disco.
-A DJ?
-Wait, Tiger Disco?
-Yes.
He runs a bar at night,
playing his own music.
But in the daytime, he opens it
for three hours as a naengmyeon place.
A three-hour naengmyeon place?
-He's a cook and a DJ?
-He's originally a cook.
HOW INTERESTING
He only makes naengmyeon in summer,
but since I can't go because of shoots,
he gives me just the broth.
When I want it but can't go out for it,
I cook some buckwheat noodles
and eat it with the broth.
And where do I end up?
-Paradise.
AMAZED
-It's his testimony.
-So you have a place for everything.
Which style do you prefer?
Hamheung or Pyongyang?
-That's Pyongyang-style.
-Pyongyang naengmyeon.
Is there a reason why you like it?
Pyongyang naengmyeon feels like
someone I had loved for a long time,
my first love.
-Right.
-Your first love?
I'd forget about it,
but it'd suddenly hit me again.
-Suddenly.
-And a particular season reminds me of it.
I recommend that
you try it on a snowy winter day.
Try eating Pyongyang naengmyeon
by the window as it snows.
-Have a bite as you look at the snow…
-How romantic.
-…with a glass of soju.
-He knows what's up.
-Recommend a place for us.
-Actually.
I like P restaurant, J restaurant,
and even U restaurant in Uijeongbu.
I don't get to go there often,
so I like to go to the place in Uijeongbu.
There's a certain excitement
while I'm on my way there.
-The anticipation?
-Yes.
-It's part of his dining experience.
-He's already dining.
The trip there is the appetizer.
On my way there, I imagine
ordering cold boiled pork in my mind.
-Gosh.
-Cold boiled pork.
And even mung bean jeon.
I run through everything in my head,
so it's exciting to see it in person.
-And if it snows…
-He's a romantic.
He wasn't like this
when he talked about his acting career.
I never knew
he was so good with his words.
His eyes are so sparkly right now.
I see some cheese down here.
-I like white wine in summer.
-You have a few.
I even purchase
boxes of the same white wine for myself.
-You get these in bulk?
-Yes.
-He buys it by the box.
-It's true.
Tell us the snacks
that are good with white wine.
I bought some Korean melons to eat
after the shoots are over.
I like to eat them
with mascarpone and olive oil.
I SEE
-It's really good.
-I think
-it'll taste a bit like vanilla.
-Right.
-Do you know what's good with white wine?
-What?
Red wine.
ON A WHOLE DIFFERENT LEVEL
Drink lots of white wine with sips of red.
DEEPLY MOVED
It's delicious.
IT'S DELICIOUS, I TELL YOU
You're creating rosé wine in your stomach.
-You have lots of veggies.
-Vegetables.
-Cilantro. Dill.
-Herbs.
These are all herbs. Parsley.
One of the things I'm going to make
after the shoots is tacos.
-I plan to make tacos with those.
-Tacos.
So cilantro is for those,
and dill is for tzatziki.
-Do you enjoy Mexican food?
-I do.
HE LOVES MEXICAN FOOD!
And as for the cilantro,
I recently tried cilantro rice.
It was probably cream sauce,
seafood, and cilantro
with long-grain rice. It was really good.
-You have long-grain rice?
-I do.
-Long-grain rice?
-There it is.
-I keep jasmine rice around.
Are you currently hooked on Mexican food?
Yes, I love it.
Is that Patrón in the freezer?
Yes! It's Patrón silver.
-Is this tequila?
-Yes.
-I got that for tacos.
-And it's in the freezer.
At this rate,
you might as well visit Mexico.
I really want to.
-I want to go see a World Cup game there,
-I see.
but my schedule wouldn't let me.
-You have to shoot the drama.
-Next to the tequila,
I kept some orange juice frozen.
WHAT ARE THESE FOR?
-You'll mix it with tequila.
-Yes!
-Instead of ice.
-It's so easy.
GOES ALL IN EVEN FOR A DRINK
I want to hang out at your place.
Come over sometime.
-You might end up there today.
-I want to go today.
-Grilled lamb skewer sauce?
-Lamb skewer.
You can use that seasoning
whenever you cook meat,
and it's good with ramyeon too.
THAT'S IT
Most people don't know that.
It turns ramyeon
into gamja-tang, pork backbone stew.
NAM-NO FALLS IN LOVE
Most people have no idea
that they go well together.
Pour instant curry
over frozen udon noodles,
sprinkle that, and microwave.
-It becomes restaurant-grade curry udon.
-Yes, exactly.
-I have garam masala next to that.
-Garam masala.
The moment you throw that into curry,
you're immediately in India.
You're right.
This episode is
so different from the last one.
There's a passionate debate going on,
but Min, you can't even take part.
Yes, I mostly order delivery food at home.
-I mean, that's amazing.
-You probably didn't know any of this.
Look at what he did with the green onion.
-Yes, all these.
-And the bread too.
He even portioned these noodles.
Noodles? Kal-guksu?
Yes, kal-guksu noodles.
EMBARRASSED
I sound way too excited.
My favorite kal-guksu place
is in Hongeun-dong.
And when I get the food to go,
they always give extra noodles,
so I always have leftovers.
I keep them frozen,
and when I make ramyeon,
I add those instead of ramyeon noodles.
-It makes the soup thicker.
-And not ramyeon noodles?
So you got everything you want to eat
ready to go right after the wrap.
-They're all waiting for me.
-They're waiting.
I wouldn't call that a fridge.
It's a curated boutique.
-It's a food boutique.
-It is a boutique.
The buyer has selected the items
to adorn the fridge with.
-All selected.
-Yes, every single one.
-Let's say it wrapped.
-So amazing.
I'll open it
and chug a can of beer immediately.
ALSO INVESTED
And then I'll make ramyeon.
-With those noodles?
-Those noodles.
And as I make the noodles,
I'll throw in thin pork belly.
YOU GET 100 POINTS OUT OF 100
I also have minced garlic,
-so a spoonful of that too.
-You need some garlic.
You need garlic in ramyeon.
Do you enjoy red meat?
-I do.
-He has lamb.
I bought the lamb
to eat as one of the fillings
when I make tacos.
Did you get these somewhere?
-They don't seem store-bought.
-No.
The way they're packed
doesn't seem like it's from a supermarket.
There's a butcher shop
I frequent in Yaksu-dong.
HE KNOWS GOOD PLACES EVERYWHERE
-All of Korea.
-Yaksu-dong.
I live alone, so I can't eat
a huge lump of meat all at once.
So when I ask the owner,
I can get them packed in single servings.
As you already know,
it doesn't taste the same
once the meat is frozen.
KIM DAE-MYUNG'S SOUL MATE
But vacuum-sealed meat will last
up to three weeks in the fridge.
-They're also waiting for the wrap.
-They are.
WHY DON'T YOU KNOW THAT I'M WAITING?
Hang in there just a little more.
-He looks so happy.
-Way too happy.
We had to get him to talk
when it came to his career.
THEY DON'T EVEN HAVE TO ASK A QUESTION NOW
We don't even have to ask him questions.
I'm thinking that he might be happier
if he steered his career to this path.
That's all for Dae-myung's fridge,
full of curated flavors!
STILL NOT OVER IT
He's all about the details
and is very serious about food.
I wonder what he wants to eat today.
Let's find out his orders first.
Show us his order!
That's a Wrap, So Head Out!
-How romantic.
-As you wait for the wrap,
what exactly are you looking for?
I like to go on a trip
whenever I'm done with a production,
but I don't think
I'll be able to do that this time.
Instead, if you recommend a dish
from a particular country
that I may want to visit, I'll eat that
and imagine that I'm there.
-Living vicariously through food?
-Yes.
-Something that tastes authentic.
A dish from a particular region.
The next one. What's the second order?
-Food, Vibe, Chefs.
-Chefs.
-Not Dae-myung, but chefs?
-Yes.
I love listening to the stories
chefs have to tell,
because eating their food
and listening to the stories
feel like a whole story.
I wanted to make that order
because I wanted to listen
to the stories you have.
-You're looking for a dish with a story.
-From their memories.
I can think of just one person
who can unravel a story
-like this one.
-Who?
The grandpa.
-He has a lot of stories to tell.
-He does.
-He's full of stories.
-He is.
He has lots of them.
Grandpa's story time.
The culinary path I have taken to this day
shows the philosophy I have as a chef.
MOVED
Of course, I'll go with Food, Vibe, Chefs.
I always convey a message
-whenever I cook.
-Sure.
-You do?
-I always include my philosophy…
-There was a message?
-…to let my guests enjoy it fully.
Today, I will take my story,
the book of my culinary journey,
and read it to you.
His life.
Grandpa's food story time.
YOU PUNK
Chef Hyun-suk is the first one
to take a spot.
Do you want to go next, Ho-young?
Sure. I'll let you
travel to Japan.
THANK YOU
He studied in Osaka.
Ho-young takes a spot at the top.
Only two chefs remain now.
-So which one?
-Jong-won.
You have many second hometowns.
Yes, he's a guy who has lots of hometowns.
EXCHANGING HOMETOWNS
I'll join the first round
and send him to a nice place.
TO A PLACE WHERE TRUMPETS SOUND?
He takes the first round.
-Sam's spot is automatically decided.
-It's automatic.
-Do you have a story to tell?
-A story?
-Me?
-A story.
Yes, there is a story I want to share.
After all,
you've starred in a music video.
Yes, he even acted.
HE HAS LOTS OF STORIES TO TELL
First, That's a Wrap, So Head Out!
Let's begin the round
between Ho-young and Jong-won!
TIME TO LEAVE FOR A CULINARY TRIP
This is the first round of cook-off
played with Dae-myung's ingredients.
Chef Son Jong-won,
who dreams of putting together
the Top Chef's Playlist,
versus Chef Jung Ho-young,
who wants to beat the top chef
and finish with the biggest twist.
Jong-won is
currently the sole first place,
and if he wins today,
he will be the first chef
to have won ten rounds.
-Already?
-Yes.
Ho-young, with five stars,
-was tied with Hyun-suk and Sung-jun.
-You're right.
The Ugliness.
KWON SUNG-JUN WINS
Sung-jun wins!
But Sung-jun won last week,
pushing both Ho-young and Hyun-suk back.
That star is a very precious one.
He gave up his looks for it.
SO FUNNY♥
Because I'm a chef.
He's like, "Because I'm a chef."
In the green room, we recorded
a very competitive conversation.
Ho-young said the chef
who has become the most evil
isn't actually Sam, but Jong-won.
ME?
His hometown changes every time,
-Right.
-…and says the things he never did before.
San Francisco and Hong Kong.
I'm quite afraid of him now.
-I see.
-Right.
-He might even start dancing very soon.
-Right?
I heard you came prepared.
A dance?
No?
Well, actually,
I can't say I haven't considered it.
HE HAS CONSIDERED DANCING
-He'll do it someday. Someday.
-It'll happen soon.
-He must've tried dancing at home.
-Actually,
movements are important
when dancing, right?
SNORT
So between JYP Entertainment,
SM Entertainment,
and YG Entertainment,
I haven't chosen which one to train with.
HE'LL PERFECT HIS DANCE
He's a perfectionist.
That means he'll come and dance
the moment he has his moves.
Even Ho-young doesn't get lessons.
I recently got a lesson
from choreographer Bae Yoon-jung herself.
You learned from her?
She told me not to tell
that she taught me.
DON'T TELL ANYONE I TAUGHT YOU
IT'S HARD TO BELIEVE THAT HE LEARNED THESE
His teacher was embarrassed by him.
THE STUDENT REJECTED BY HIS TEACHER
I also hear
Jong-won has been trembling in fear
in preparation for this round.
What's up?
Ho-young seems to have
-an extra cooking tool in the studio.
-Right.
-The human tool.
-Something new?
-It's a one-on-two fight.
-I am also
known as the peddler of the show
because I bring so many things,
but he always uses
a huge-sized tool
that can't even compare to mine.
A HUGE KITCHEN TOOL?
SOMEBODY KIM
-You're sitting in front of him again?
-Ho-young.
It just happened.
So if it's all right with him,
I'd like to add another tool too.
-Is it a person?
-It is.
-So it's a kitchen toolman.
-A kitchen toolman.
Not the kitchen staff, but a toolman.
-At least he calls it human.
-Kitchen toolman.
Ho-young uses Sam, so who will you use?
Nam-no, help me!
Yes, sir!
-They'll either both use one or none.
-It's practically a team round.
-I think I'll need him for something.
-So you do need Sam.
CHEF HO-YOUNG'S INGREDIENTS:
LAMB, SHRIMP, NOODLES, CHERRY TOMATO
CILANTRO, MINI BELL PEPPER, LETTUCE,
CURRY BLOCK, GARAM MASALA, AND MORE
What are you making, Chef Ho-young?
The name of my dish is
BOOMBALAMB!
He tries too hard.
Both guests are in shock.
-BLACKPINK?
-What was that?
"BOOMBAYAH" by BLACKPINK.
-I'll make a lamb dish.
-BOOMBALAMB.
Dae-myung said…
-If you're dizzy, take a break.
-Okay.
-You look dizzy.
-The blood rushed to his head.
I want to make
a lamb dish to send Dae-myung
to Sapporo.
In July,
-the weather is cool and nice there.
-It's better in summer.
So Sapporo is pretty great right now.
As an appetizer,
I'll serve chilled noodles
you can dip in sesame sauce,
a Japanese cold somen dish.
Next, you had some lamb,
so I'll grind it and make lamb hambagu,
Japanese-style lamb hamburger steak.
Lastly, soup curry is famous there.
-Even soup curry?
-Three dishes?
I'll use the bugeo-guk broth
-you got from Mugyo-dong,
-As the base?
…and make a rich soup curry.
That sounds so delicious.
CHEF JONG-WON'S INGREDIENTS:
PORK BELLY, SHRIMP, MANILA CLAM
CILANTRO, AVOCADO, TORTILLA,
WHOLE TOMATO, CABBAGE, BAY LEAF, AND MORE
Chef Jong-won, what will you make
to fight against him?
As I listened to Dae-myung talk,
he seemed to love Mexican food.
In Mexico, there's an area
called Baja California,
which is a long peninsula
in the northwestern part.
There is lots of great seafood there,
so I want you to eat this
and visit the country yourself.
That's why my dish is called
You Go to Mexico.
-You Go to Mexico.
-Yes.
It's You Go to Mexico,
not, "You go to Hawaii."
I'll make tacos
and something called pozole,
which is Mexican soup.
I think it's similar
to sundae-guk in Korea.
So I'll make that soup
with pork belly and naengmyeon broth.
Also, there's a cocktail called michelada.
It's uniquely made with beer
-and clam juice.
-What?
-Clam juice?
-I want you to imagine
having tacos, pozole, and a cold cocktail
as you sit and rest on the beach.
I want to help you experience
that vacation spot vibe.
-Gosh.
-Chef Jong-won.
What's this
about you almost changing your name?
As I mentioned, I really love tacos,
so I considered changing my name
-from Son Jong-won to Son Tak-ho.
-Son Tak-ho?
-Tak-ho.
-Son Tak-ho.
Not only is he changing his hometown,
but he's now changing his name.
HE HAS COME A LONG WAY
-He's no joke with his words now.
-Chef Ho-young.
Shouldn't you think of a new name too?
I also love
-Sapporo very much.
-Yes?
So how about Jung Ppo-ro?
-Good job! You have to keep going with it.
-That's what you do.
-It's Son Tak-ho versus Jung Ppo-ro.
-Jung Ppo-ro.
-Tak-ho versus Ppo-ro.
-Sounds great.
Then now, let us begin
the cook-off between these two.
"Ogenki desu ka?"
Here to send Dae-myung to Sapporo,
Chef Jung Ppo-ro is up.
"You go to Mexico."
Chef Son Tak-ho is also here
to send Dae-myung to a beach in Mexico.
Will it be Japan or Mexico?
Let the 15-minute cook-off begin!
Jung Ppo-ro and Son Tak-ho.
SON TAK-HO VS. JUNG PPO-RO
MANILA CLAM MEAT
He's making clam stock first.
It makes no sense
to mix clam juice with beer.
-Nam-no, I need your help.
-Yes, sir.
Take this and crush these.
His kitchen toolman is helping out.
CHILI PEPPER, GARLIC
CHILI PEPPER & GARLIC
-And just crush these?
-Crush them.
ONION
-Nam-no does his best to help.
-These too, Nam-no.
ONION
I'm making guacamole,
so he's crushing chili pepper,
garlic, onion, and cilantro.
-Pepper and garlic. It's tedious work.
-The aroma
is completely different
when the ingredients are mashed.
-It changes the texture and the aroma.
-And the texture.
HOW'S TEAM SAPPORO DOING?
-One second.
-What do I do?
Not yet.
-Not yet?
-No.
1. MAKE MIXTURE FOR LAMB PATTY
BY GRINDING LAMB, ONION,
EGG WHITE, AND OYSTER SAUCE
-Ho-young's grinding something.
-Lamb patty.
It's lamb, oyster sauce, and onion.
Can you keep us updated as his toolman?
Sure thing.
ACCEPTS HIS FATE AS TOOLMAN
Put this and this in here
and blend it for me.
-One tsuyu. And?
-Yes.
One tsuyu, one soy milk.
A spoonful of peanut butter.
Put them together
and blend.
MAKING USE OF HIS TOOLMAN
I think he's making the sauce.
Look at the sidekicks.
-The kitchen tool match.
-The toolmen.
-He's using lamb now.
-Lamb.
Chef Ho-young makes curry.
-From Mugyo-dong.
-You were planning to eat that later,
-and he's using it as broth.
-Yes.
-I wonder what that's like.
-Did you add the curry block?
-Yes, and a bit of garam masala.
-The curry block?
Garam masala. Wow.
The moment you add it,
it takes you abroad, to India.
TAK-HO CAN ALSO FOCUS THANKS TO NAM-NO
PORK BELLY
CRUSHED GARLIC, TEQUILA, SALSA VERDE
He just added rice.
Yes, he just added rice to the pot.
Tomato?
-He added rice and sauce to the pot.
-Bay leaf.
What are you making, Tak-ho?
I'm making pozole,
which is pretty much
Mexico's favorite soup.
It's usually made with beans or corn,
but I'm using instant rice.
-Pozole.
-It's like gukbap, rice soup.
Is that his naengmyeon broth?
I just added that.
-He's using naengmyeon broth.
-Yes.
-Son Tak uses naengmyeon broth.
-"Son Tak?"
-Ppo-ro uses…
-Bugeo-guk soup.
Naengmyeon broth versus bugeo-guk soup.
It has to be better
than the original broths.
It smells so good.
You have to use a mortar
to maximize the aroma.
Should I continue?
Add avocado to it.
A MUST FOR MEXICAN FOOD, AVOCADO!
MASHING AVOCADO TOO
HE'S CHECKING THE SAUCE…
It's too salty. More soy milk.
-One more soy milk?
-Yes.
BLENDING AGAIN
Is this okay?
One more time. Some more soy milk.
There's no more. That was it.
I used everything.
Then water it is.
PUTS CHEF SOMEONE UP FOR THE JOB…
AND GOES BACK TO COOKING
ADDING CILANTRO!
-Are you mixing cilantro and lamb?
-Yes, it's cilantro.
That sounds delicious.
There's the lamb patty.
That looks so good.
Chef Ho-young's hambagu is to die for.
-It's guaranteed to be good.
-Yes.
You have about nine minutes left.
Six minutes have gone by.
1. MIX FLOUR, BEER, EGG TO MAKE BATTER
Wait, what's that?
Ramyeon soup base?
-What? Ramyeon soup base?
-He's using it out in the open.
-What am I supposed to do now?
-Everyone uses it now.
All these chefs are doing that.
It's not like that, actually.
Mexican food requires ancho chile pepper,
and the closest thing to that
was this ramyeon soup base, in my opinion.
It can give that flavor.
-I need that smoky flavor.
-That's true.
I guess it's not a bad idea
to use it adequately.
Chef Tak-ho is
currently deep-frying shrimp.
Tacos are often made with fried fish,
but I'll use shrimp today.
Chef Jong-won, I'll add these too.
Whoa.
He might as well
go behind the kitchen counter.
Did you say something, Sam?
-That he might as well go join him.
-At this rate, right?
Control yourself, Nam-no.
-Sit down, Nam-no.
-Sit down.
You are not allowed to show your bums.
I never lifted my bottoms.
YEAH, GOOD JOB…
-Even the toolmen are bickering.
-I guess.
Are you helping more?
Or am I helping more?
Telling each other to keep it moderate.
Jong-won's toolman
finished making guacamole.
LEMON JUICE
SALT
That guacamole looks so good.
Am I done here?
-You are.
-Okay.
THE TOOLMAN IS DONE, NOW WHAT?
I'll have some soda.
GLUG GLUG
FROM A TOOLMAN TO A MUKBANGER
HOW ABOUT MR. JUNG PPO-RO?
MINI BELL PEPPERS
AND SHRIMPS
Take these.
-Alternate between them.
-Okay.
Like this?
LAUGHING AT THE OTHER TOOLMAN
Don't you think doing this
is the same as cooking over there?
THAT'S WHAT WE'RE SAYING
What are you up to, Sam?
He told me to put these on the sticks.
-Like skewers?
-Yes.
WHAT'S HO-YOUNG DOING NOW?
-Noodles?
-Noodles.
Why did he bundle them up in the center?
If you wet the tip and hold it tightly,
the noodles will keep their shape
as they're cooked.
You can do that?
AMAZED
Look, Ho-young.
-Is this it?
-Good.
HANDING OVER SKEWERS
Chef Ho-young now cooks the skewers
which his toolman
put together with care.
They look great.
Am I done?
Yes, you can relax.
You have six minutes and ten seconds.
He's making tacos.
HE'S JULIENNING TORTILLAS?
Oddly, Chef Jong-won
just julienned the taco shells.
PULLING OUT FRIED SHRIMPS
-Really?
-Look at the fritters.
They look great.
-He cut them like that?
-I think he's deep-frying those.
Yes, it's for the soup.
-The garnish on top.
-Yes.
4. MAKE SALSA WITH ONION,
CHEONGYANG PEPPER, WHOLE TOMATO, CILANTRO
That salsa looks so good.
Will his dishes
taste authentically Mexican?
Tortillas burn easily,
so you'd better check.
I'm keeping my eyes on it.
What he's making surely looks good.
JUNG PPO-RO STEPS UP!
-That looks good.
-It smells great.
Latin American style
is different from Asian style.
This one. The soup curry.
What does it taste like?
It's like curry but soup.
-Have you had it?
-Of course.
-In Sapporo?
-Yes, two, three times.
Then you can make a comparison.
He has had it in Sapporo.
-Have you been to Mexico?
-I have not.
That means
you wouldn't know,
no matter how the dishes turn out.
GOOD NEWS
-He can't confirm.
-He has the upper hand.
It's authentic Mexican.
-He says it's authentic Mexican.
-It's authentic.
-Authentic.
-Please make it authentic.
Like a Mexican grandma's cooking.
-A Mexican grandma?
-A Mexican grandma's cooking.
What's her name?
I forgot.
Wait a second.
Are those burnt?
No, no.
-No? They look burnt.
-They aren't.
Aren't they burnt?
-No.
-I told you so!
I said they burn easily!
Sung-ju, please report from the kitchen.
-Let me check and see if it's burnt.
-I told you to keep an eye on them!
I think he's only claiming
this is authentic Mexican.
He's making new ones.
-They're burnt!
-They are burnt!
See? I told you that they'd burn!
-Stop it, Poong!
-I clearly told you so!
-This one.
-It's burnt. Don't eat it.
Is it burnt?
It's burnt.
IT'S BURNT
-See?
-Spit it out.
-You can always do it over.
-These are burnt.
-The noodles turned out like this.
-The noodles.
THEY WERE COOKED IN SHAPE
Can you…
-Can you cook noodles like that?
-You're right.
He wet one tip of the noodles
and pressed them together,
so they got stuck on each other.
Once he put it in the water,
it kept its shape and got cooked.
-He glued them together on purpose.
-That's what you did?
-Whoa. That's cool.
-That's cool.
A high-level technique.
The soup curry.
Sapporo's soup curry.
Are you in Sapporo right now?
Or are you still in the studio?
I can find curry like this
even in my neighborhood.
IT'S AN EMERGENCY
It doesn't feel like Sapporo.
He should've just eaten the bugeo-guk.
-He put something in.
-How is it different?
He used lamb.
He added lamb? Right now?
It already had chunks of meat inside,
but I added more just now.
Three minutes!
WHAT'S HE STRAINING?
What's that, Jong-won?
The clam broth turned out nicely.
He made clam broth.
I'm about to turn it into a cocktail.
I wonder what it'll be like
one that's mixed with beer.
-It sounds strange.
-It's hard to imagine.
Three minutes!
Three minutes left.
He's rimming the glass!
What's he doing?
He's coating the rim with powder.
-A cocktail technique.
-Is that Mexican?
-It's done with salt for tequila.
-Right.
-It looks like ramyeon soup base.
-Is that ramyeon soup base?
Is that ramyeon soup base?
My friend José told me
to always use S brand's ramyeon.
SAYS JOSÉ
You'll make him lick the powder itself?
ANOTHER ATTEMPT TO BRING IN HIS FRIEND
Even I couldn't think of that!
José. José told me that.
Who in the world is this José?
He makes great tequila cocktails.
JOSÉ THE TEQUILA BOY
He's using ramyeon soup base
out in the open.
This is pozole, a Mexican soup.
Was pozole
made by Son Jong-won or Son Tak-ho?
It was Son Tak-ho.
It tastes like a Mexican dish.
-Ice.
STEAK SAUCE
He's using steak sauce.
It's similar to Bloody Mary.
-Are you going to add beer now?
-He's pouring beer on top.
A DASH OF BEER ON TOP
-Beer wasn't the main ingredient.
-Right?
He's using only a bit of beer.
A minute and 43 seconds.
I can do this.
You don't have much time.
-Tacos.
-It's like ground pepper.
6. MAKE SOUR CREAM WITH YOGURT,
CHERRY PEPPER CREAM CHEESE, LEMON JUICE
CURRY ALWAYS COMES WITH RICE!
BEGINS TO PLATE HIS FOOD!
ABOUT TO FINISH THE SOUP CURRY!
Over here. Try that.
Let me try this once again.
DID THE FLAVOR CHANGE?
Was it made by Jung Ho-young
or Jung Ppo-ro?
It's different now. It's by Jung Ppo-ro.
-There's a hint of Sapporo.
-Really? Has it changed?
-It's different from ordinary curry.
-It is?
The tortillas?
-Oh, no!
-Goodness!
Are those burnt?
-Are those burnt?
-They're burnt!
-No? Can he eat these?
-No, it has to be charred like this.
How's that authentic Mexican?
Sanchez told me to do this.
But it's true. It was Sanchez?
Wasn't it José?
-He says tacos are better charred.
-Sure.
Goodness, Son Tak-ho.
One minute.
-It's stuck!
-It's burnt!
IT'S STUCK?
Sanchez said
you do that with the last piece.
A TORTILLA MUST BE STUCK TO MAKE TACOS!
He's usually not like that.
He's saying these are fine.
What are you doing?
Are you trying to eat it?
Thirty-eight seconds!
THE NOODLE SAUCE SOMEONE MADE FOR HIM
PLATING THE SAUCE FIRST
Thirty-seven seconds.
He's topping the curry with skewers.
You have to finish up.
Thirty seconds!
LAMB HAMBAGU IS SERVED
ON TOP OF A TABLETOP GRILL
Twenty seconds.
Please start plating your food now.
Can you put the soup here?
Take this and put the pozole here.
JONG-WON MAKES TACOS!
You don't have much time.
Twenty seconds!
That shrimp look great.
Please plate your dishes and wrap up!
He's topping them
with delicious ingredients.
RETRIEVING THE INSTANT RICE!
Please plate your dishes.
-All done.
-Ten. Nine.
-Ho-young's done.
-Eight. Seven.
-Six.
-The ladle.
-Five.
WHAT WILL HAPPEN TO THE MEXICAN MEAL?
-One!
-Time's up.
-He's done. Ring the bell.
-The bell.
-Please plate your dishes.
-Jong-won finishes too.
-Careful.
They both look amazing. It's insane.
OFF TO AN OVERSEAS TRIP!
Both meals were finished.
The shrimp.
That was amazing.
These look so good.
They're the best yet.
You're lucky to be here today.
Have me here as a guest too.
GASP
Both meals were finished
just for Dae-myung.
I'm finding it hard to believe
that they made this with my ingredients.
It's like a miracle.
Now, please start
with Chef Jung Ppo-ro's dish,
-Jung Ppo-ro?
-…BOOMBALAMB.
NEATLY PRESENTED COLD NOODLES
WITH SPECIAL SAUCE
SOUP CURRY WITH SAPPORO VIBES
AND SKEWERS ON TOP
DELICIOUSLY JUICY LAMB HAMBAGU
CHEF JUNG PPO-RO'S BOOMBALAMB
He's now in Sapporo.
Should I dip the noodles all the way in?
Dip it all the way in and eat it.
The noodles look so nice.
-You can make it look so neat?
-Say something in Japanese by his side.
He's in Sapporo, so speak Japanese.
-Does it taste all right?
-It does.
Oh.
It's very delicious.
-Thank you.
-It feels like Sapporo.
-Did you add peanut sauce?
-Yes.
I blended soy milk,
peanut butter, and tsuyu.
-It's tsuyu.
THIS TIME, HE DIPS IT ALL THE WAY IN
SLURP
EYES SHUT
-It's soba.
-Soup curry.
What's wrong?
-It's so good.
-Is it?
NICE
I've never had a sauce like this.
I made it.
IF IT'S GOOD, IT'S THANKS TO ME
-That's cheating!
-He finally spoke up.
-You can't do this.
-You should've made it, Ho-young.
-I did do as I was told.
-I tasted it.
-And next.
-Okay.
He was already moved
after eating the noodles.
That's lamb hambagu.
I added some chopped cilantro roots.
Lamb and cilantro go very well together.
TAKING A BIG BITE
Lamb hambagu.
-It could smell.
-He's smiling.
-It looks good.
-It made him smile.
Was cilantro for that?
-Gosh.
-What is it?
-It's unbelievably good.
-Unbelievably good?
Does it smell like lamb?
That smell hits you so sweetly.
I want to try some.
Did cilantro play a role?
Yes, it definitely brings out
the lamb's aroma
-even more nicely.
-Cilantro?
Two different flavors
are hitting me at once,
and it's so delicious.
Whenever I go to Sapporo,
I always go to that famous D lamb place.
This is even better than their dish.
Jung Ppo-ro.
He's in Sapporo now.
You don't have to go there anymore.
-Sapporo is right here.
-It's right here. This is Sapporo.
I actually brought my passport.
OH, MAN
Let me see it. I'll stamp it for you.
-The immigration process.
-Wait, really?
Is he going to do this?
-He's the immigration officer.
-You brought it?
-What?
-He really brought it.
-Is he going to do this?
HIS ACTUAL PASSPORT
-What?
-I thought it was a joke.
-No way.
-Are you serious?
It's so weird to see him
pull it out of his pocket.
So you can take things this far?
SHOWING OFF HIS PASSPORT
You didn't expect that, right?
-It was just a joke.
-That was random.
Do you always keep it with you?
-I always have it in my bag.
-Why?
When I suddenly become free
for a couple of days,
I'd take a quick flight
to places like Fukuoka.
AGAIN, HE'S INSANE
So which country will I end up going to?
Will it be Mexico or Japan?
-Next, soup curry.
-Let me try the soup curry now.
First, try the shrimp skewer.
Then have some rice with the curry
with a piece of hambagu on top.
GOSH…
I can already picture it in my head.
SHRIMP SKEWERS SOAKED IN SOUP CURRY
Jeez. That looks so good.
It's still steaming.
EATS THE BELL PEPPER AND SHRIMP AT ONCE
It must be hot.
SMACKING LIPS
And now…
That mix is a win.
You can top it with curry as you like.
-There's meat in the curry too.
-There is.
-It's lamb.
-There's lamb in there?
The curry tasted different.
I can't deal with this anymore.
ON TOP OF EVERYTHING
-He loves cilantro.
-That's what I call a trip.
I agree.
THE VISUAL MAKES EVERYONE SHUDDER
He'll try it like that.
-Soup curry and…
-Like this.
-My mouth is watering.
-It looks good.
Rice and cilantro.
How amazing!
AS IF HE'S ACTUALLY IN JAPAN
Master, thank you.
APPROVED AS CURRY MASTER
Thank you.
-You've had soup curry in Sapporo.
-Yes.
Does it taste similar?
The flavor is much more profound.
The soup curry I had in Sapporo
was far thinner than this.
-Was it thin?
-It was.
-Yes.
-It's like watery soup.
It's kind of like Pyongyang naengmyeon,
because you're mostly unsure
until you're addicted by the end.
But this hits me directly with flavors.
It's like, "I am soup curry!"
BOOMBALAMB HAS A STRONG PRESENCE
Oishiteru.
Oishiteru?
Isn't it aishiteru? Meaning "I love you?"
-It's lovely and delicious.
-Oishii plus aishiteru. Oishiteru.
Become delicious!
This is so delicious.
-I'm about to tear up.
-He's about to cry.
Tears are gushing!
Gushing!
-Why don't you go to Mexico now?
-Shall we go to Mexico?
This time, please try
Chef Son Tak-ho's You Go to Mexico.
AUTHENTIC TACOS ON THE BEACH IN MEXICO!
MEXICAN SOUP, MEXICAN COCKTAIL,
YOGURT SOUR CREAM
CHEF SON TAK-HO'S YOU GO TO MEXICO
-Thank you. I'll have a bite.
-He's trying the taco.
-Dip it in the sauce.
-In the sauce.
One, two, three, four.
You're now in Mexico.
USING EVERY SPANISH WORD HE KNOWS
Rodriguez!
-Rodriguez!
DIPS IT IN THE SOUR CREAM
AND TAKES A BIG BITE
He's digging in.
ENJOYING THE TACO FLAVOR
FILLING UP HIS MOUTH
Oh, gosh.
-Is it good?
-Thank you so much.
You're welcome.
"Thank you so much."
THANK YOU FOR TRANSLATING
I got hooked on tacos
and did a tour around Seoul
to visit every famous taco joint.
There's a place in Sangsu
called G restaurant,
which is my favorite.
I've heard that their food is
similar to what they have in Mexico.
It's more delicious than that.
-José's recipe worked.
-That's José.
The sour flavor of this sauce
balances out the fried shrimp
and creates a perfect harmony.
Gosh, it's so good.
What should I eat next?
-Try a sip of michelada.
-The cocktail.
A cocktail made with clam juice.
That's a great idea. Glasses usually
get rimmed with salt for tequila, right?
-Ramyeon soup base would be good too.
-The soup base.
This might be even better.
Will it go well with the cocktail?
GULPING DOWN
A cocktail and ramyeon soup base.
He used clam broth, right?
-And beer.
-Yes, and beer.
Do you like it?
That's it.
What is it?
It's made with tomato,
but it's very sour,
about twice as much as ketchup.
And when the umami from
the ramyeon soup base meets the drink,
-it becomes the flavor of the sun.
-Flavor of the sun.
-He's talking about Sun Chips!
-Does it feel like…
-…you're tanning on the beach?
-Sun Chips?
There's a salsa party happening
right in front of my eyes.
A salsa party! It's a salsa party!
OH, MY…
-Gonzales!
-Yes!
One, two, three, four!
THE MEXICO VIBES ARE OFF THE WALL
Did you drink during the break?
Whatever! Just keep going!
GONZALES LOOKS VERY EXCITED
You're giving great vibes.
Great Mexican vibes.
WE'RE IN MEXICO RIGHT NOW
Oh, man.
-Is this next?
-Yes, but wait.
I wanted to let you enjoy it chilled,
so I got the tequila you love
from your freezer.
Let me serve it in the smaller glass
-with a hint of Korea.
-He had served another cup.
Tequila is gushing out!
POONG HAS COME UNDONE
-He's totally insane today.
-He's out of his mind.
Tequila gushes out.
I can't help but grab my passport.
He was on his way to Sapporo.
-Gosh.
-Oh, no.
Have a bite of the Mexican gukbap, pozole,
and then take the tequila shot,
as if it's soju.
Mexico's household soup, pozole.
CLOSES HIS EYES AND SAVORS THE FLAVOR
-Looks good.
-What is it like?
He used rice to make it.
He already felt a hint of Mexico earlier.
The tequila!
EXHILARATING
The umami from the soup hides in my mouth,
and the moment tequila comes in,
there's a salsa party in my mouth.
A salsa party.
-A salsa party?
-There's a salsa party in his mouth.
It's in my mouth.
FEELING THE VIBES AGAIN
It's in his mouth.
Amigo!
HAPPINESS INDEX, 100
I'm already so happy right now,
-so is there a need to go to Mexico?
-Right?
-You can eat this right here.
-It's Mexico right here.
Call Poong
whenever you want to go to Mexico.
-I will do that.
-Chef Tak-ho's tacos can do that to you.
…CHUCKLE
Why are you smiling that big?
I didn't know this show was like this.
THE SHOW'S FULL OF VIBES
Why don't we let Min have a bite?
Me? Yes, please.
-It's really good.
-It is?
That's Chef Ho-young's dish,
BOOMBALAMB.
The noodles look so pretty,
kept so neat even after cooking.
-He glued the tip together.
-They usually stick to one another.
It's so strange.
-Mmm.
-So…
Does it taste worthy
of what Dae-myung said?
I can't express myself
the way that he did.
-You can't go that far?
-It's not that.
I agree with his review.
It tastes light, yet very delicious.
-Try this.
-I've been wondering what it's like.
It's so new.
AMAZED
-It's good. It's so good.
-Is it?
It's good.
EVERYONE IS AUTOMATICALLY AMAZED
I made that.
A BIG BITE OF THE LAMB HAMBAGU
Mmm!
This is really good.
I'M TELLING YOU!
Something about that cilantro smell.
The thing you said.
FULLY CONVINCED
Wait, over there.
-It's not a restaurant.
-It's amazing.
A BUSTLING SOUP CURRY JOINT
What's it like, you three?
-Mmm.
-The soup curry.
It goes really well with lamb,
-and the thickness is perfect.
-It is.
It can't be too thin or thick.
The curry's good,
but the noodles were amazing.
The Sam Kim sauce is great.
-I made that.
-The Sam Kim sauce?
APPROVED
As we speak,
Min's taking a bite of the taco.
-I'll eat it too.
-It fills his mouth.
WHOA
This has
a richer flavor of aroma,
and it hits me much harder.
FULL OF MEXICAN FLAVORS AND AROMAS
I haven't had many tacos.
So this is what it's like.
It's really good.
ADDICTED TO AUTHENTIC TACOS
TAKING A BIG BITE
Hmm?
Is it to die for?
This is good too.
MOUTHS FULL WITH TACOS
Mmm!
It's awfully delicious.
My appetite is on.
How will you pick, Dae-myung?
-What do I do?
-Oh…
It's now time to make a choice.
Choose one to go to Mexico with Son Tak-ho
and two to go to Japan with Jung Ppo-ro.
Make your decision
and press the button!
I won't be able to choose.
IT'S NOT AN EASY DECISION…
AFTER MUCH THOUGHT
-Okay. I did.
-Did you press one?
All right.
Which chef did Dae-myung choose?
Let's check out the result!
RESULT ANNOUNCEMENT
His drama wrapped,
and he wants to go on a trip.
Will he go to Mexico,
or will it be Japan?
Who did Dae-myung choose?
Which country is it?
Is it Japan or Mexico?
Jung Ppo-ro or Son Tak-ho?
Dae-myung's choice!
JUNG HO-YOUNG WINS
He's off to Japan!
CHEF JUNG PPO-RO'S BOOMBALAMB WINS
-Sapporo!
-To Sapporo, Jung Ppo-ro!
THE SAPPORO DISH CAPTURED HIM
-This is way too good. It's insane.
-Jung Ppo-ro wins.
I often go to Sapporo in winter
to see the snow.
-Right.
-But this dish
made me curious about Sapporo in summer,
something I have never seen before.
I see.
-And it's summer now.
-Agreed.
-First off,
thank you so much for choosing me.
Sam helped me out big time too.
PLEASED
You were urging him to mention you.
-Shouldn't Sam get the star?
-Right?
I'll take it in his place.
He just stood up.
THE VERSATILE KITCHEN TOOLMAN
This means
Chef Son Tak-ho is stuck with nine stars.
He's been jinxed.
You must feel rather uneasy.
Here's to my friends
who are watching this in Mexico.
Sanchez, José,
-and Rodriguez.
-Didn't he imagine them?
I'm sorry, guys.
Please put a star on Chef Jung Ho-young!
Ho-young and Sung-jun are now in a tie!
This is a very significant star.
DAE-MYUNG ARRIVES AT SAPPORO!
He has arrived in Japan.
This is the second cook-off
with ingredients from Dae-myung's fridge.
Chef Choi Hyun-suk, a 55-year-old grandpa
with many stories to tell,
versus Chef Sam Kim,
who's only talkative in the green room.
-He's our host.
-The Yu Jae-seok of the green room.
He's good.
-This is a classic rival match.
-A classic rival match.
Unfitting of that grand title,
one of the two chefs
has had an overwhelming win.
WHO IS IT?
Chef Hyun-suk has lost
four rounds in a row against Chef Sam.
EVEN SURPRISED HIMSELF
-Is that why he has a lot pent up inside?
-He does?
-He said this in the green room.
-Ah-ha.
I'm sure that's the case.
CAN HAPPEN AFTER 4 LOSSES
"It's about time
people stopped calling Sam a saint."
"He has been corrupted."
-What do you mean?
-That's strange.
During our first season,
he always cooked with his philosophy,
no matter what.
He did.
-Naturalism. Healthy food.
-Yes, right. Naturalism.
He never compromised.
But that man
has changed since this year.
He's now consumed by stars.
He doesn't care
about the ways, means, or ingredients.
He throws everything in.
So he's now nicknamed SO Chef.
CHEF JONG-WON?
-SO Chef?
SO Chef?
This was the first time
Chef Jong-won butt into our banter.
-So you could do that?
-He had a lot bottled up too.
-He had only watched us until now.
-Right.
I chimed in, thinking I was funny.
-But it wasn't that good. Sorry.
-Nice try.
SO Chef wasn't so bad.
-Star-Obsessed Chef.
-Good try.
-SO Chef.
Chef Sam, there are these allegations,
so we'd like to hear
your official stand on this.
I don't know.
I wouldn't say I'm consumed by stars.
As the kids say, I'm following the trend.
NOW CORRUPT AND ELOQUENT
He's better with words too.
Just now, Chef Jong-won chiming in
and joining the banter
was so funny.
I feel like he has moved over…
…a little closer to our world.
I feel like we're closer.
Yes, we all grow closer over banter.
-So Jong-won is changing, not you?
-You're good.
He has changed so much.
You didn't expect this, right?
-It's very entertaining.
-The chefs jabbing, I mean.
THE ENTERTAINING WORLD OF BANTER
For your cook-off,
you're to make something
with a backstory of your own.
So you have to weave
your story into the dish,
and I wonder what they have in store.
CHEF HYUN-SUK'S INGREDIENTS:
CAPELLINI, BEEF TENDERLOIN, SHRIMP
WEBFOOT OCTOPUS, BASIL, PARSLEY,
OLIVE, AVOCADO, APPLE, AND MORE
You're up first, Chef Hyun-suk.
What are you making?
The dish I'll make is
Annals of the Choi Hyun-suk Dynasty.
-Annals of the Choi Hyun-suk Dynasty?
-Not the Annals of the Joseon Dynasty.
-Not Joseon.
My philosophy in culinary arts
has formed about 21 years ago.
I studied under my teacher for a decade,
then finally opened my own place
and became the head chef.
And this review changed my entire career.
It said my food was delicious,
but most of it overlapped
with my previous restaurant, La Cucina.
So I told myself I'd make something
that nobody else would,
-and I came up with cold capellini.
-Cold capellini.
-His signature dish.
-Because 21 years ago,
no one really ate pasta cold.
Back then, I was nicknamed the Crazy Chef.
-Yes.
-And since that time,
I've changed my menu monthly
and never stopped inventing new dishes,
which developed me
into the creative chef you're seeing now
Today, I'd like to present
the chronological changes
in my history in a single dish.
DEEPLY MOVED♥
Then can we say cold capellini
was the first dish you created?
Yes, the first creative dish I made
was cold pasta.
There's a picture he sent us.
It'll help you stay immersed in his story.
These are his old pictures.
Wait a second.
THESE AREN'T PHOTOS OF COLD CAPELLINI
-No pictures of his pasta?
-That's not the dish.
EXCUSE ME, CHEF HYUN-SUK
You're supposed to show us
photos related to your restaurant.
-Show us the pasta.
-He's trying to show us
that he used to be thin like capellini.
He's more like penne now.
I'll send the pictures of the pasta
and let the viewers see it
by the time this episode is on air.
That was so random.
I think he showed that to tell us,
"Stop calling me grandpa."
CHEF SAM'S INGREDIENTS:
KIMCHI, TORTILLA, BEEF SIRLOIN
BEEF TENDERLOIN, BRISKET,
CHERRY TOMATO, CILANTRO, AND MORE
The name of my dish is
-Tails of Mexican Tales.
-Like the show Tails of Tales?
-Yes.
Because my tale
has many tails to go off on.
It's a pretty long story.
Tails of Mexican Tales?
-It's a story of my friend.
-Your friend?
His name is Charlo Martinez,
and we became friends
while working together
when I first started my culinary career.
He always made me burritos.
-Burritos.
And when I made something,
I'd make kimchi fried rice.
He really loved
eating that with roasted seaweed.
That's a good mix.
Actually, it's a pretty long story.
Sam!
I'm sorry, but if it's a long story,
may I sit down?
-Sit down.
-His blood sugar is dropping.
-But I listened to his story!
-You're so selfish.
He's serious. It's so sad.
WE KNOW YOU'RE STILL GOING STRONG
-Your Mexican friend.
-Oh, yes.
We became very close,
and he also began to cook seriously.
After some time, we parted ways.
Fifteen years after that,
when I went back to America and met him,
he gave me a picture
the two of us took together.
I miss him a lot,
so I'm going to make
a burrito with kimchi fried rice filling.
-Huh?
-Kimchi burrito.
-It sounds like
you suddenly came up
with Tails of Mexican Tales
after learning that
Dae-myung is into Mexican food.
You are consumed by stars.
Not at all.
I even have our picture
from when we worked together.
-If he has photo proof, it must be true.
-There he is.
A PHOTO FROM CHARLO
Really? Back then?
You had short hair?
-I shaved it off when I became a cook.
-I see.
The photo on the left
is during the 2002 World Cup season,
when he cheered for Korea with me
on the day of Jung-hwan's historic goal.
Sorry, but doesn't that mean
I'm why he became a chef?
-No.
-You're right.
-That's true.
-He must've taken interest in Korea.
You'll see the Red Devils T-shirt there.
-The Red Devils shirt.
-The Red Devils.
-That's a must.
-A must.
And that's the photo from a decade after.
-Yes, in 2024.
-Only 2 years ago.
-Wait, are you wearing a microphone?
-What?
-Were you filming? We got you.
-Yes.
-It was for a documentary.
-Oh, back then.
I think I saw him as an actor
on a reenactment show.
You're mistaken.
Well, there are a few parts
we're still suspicious of.
-It's odd that you're making Mexican food.
-Right?
That's why I want to use
my kimchi fried rice as the filling
and roll up a burrito
just like Charlo used to do for me.
A mix of two memories.
MEMORIES WITH HIS MEXICAN FRIEND
He'll think of Martinez as he cooks.
And now,
let us begin the next round,
Food, Vibe, Chefs.
Nicknamed the SO Chef,
the Star-Obsessed Chef, Sam Kim.
Versus another SO Chef,
-the Self-Obsessed Chef, Hyun-suk.
-Self-Obsessed?
Which one of the two will become
the storyteller to win Dae-myung's heart?
Let the 15-minute cook-off begin!
A STORYTELLING ROUND!
SAM BEGINS BY WARMING UP INSTANT RICE
-Hoping to see some heartwarming dishes.
-What's he doing?
-Basil.
-Basil?
-I'm making basil pesto.
-Basil pesto.
But mine has a different recipe.
-Huh? How is it different?
-How is it different?
-I add parsley.
-Parsley.
Curly parsley adds
a nice green aroma and a darker color.
-So he adds parsley.
-It can be too strong, so not too much.
Are you making fresh pasta?
Capellini is a kind of thin pasta,
-so it gets soggy quickly.
-Right.
So I'm using dried noodles.
Hmm.
Okay.
DISAPPOINTED…
-Fresh pasta would've been more moving.
-Right?
-Even if it's thin.
-Yes.
-I mean, dried pasta?
-He makes linguine.
-I can't lie to make this more moving.
-There's a story here.
GUILTY AS CHARGED
That pasta may not have been around
-twenty-one years ago.
-Exactly.
It'd be great if someone could hold this.
THE TOOL GETS REPLACED
This is becoming a new fad.
A MUST-HAVE GADGET: KITCHEN TOOLMAN
Now, the SO Chef
-has to make a burrito.
-He does.
But first, kimchi fried rice.
Kimchi burrito sounds good.
1. STIR-FRY ONION, GREEN ONION,
BEEF SIRLOIN, AND MINCED GARLIC
That's beef.
-Is that sirloin?
-It is.
HYUN-SUK MAKES THE PASTA SAUCE!
OLIVE
Olives and anchovy paste.
-Olives, anchovy paste, and oil.
-Oil.
FINISHED!
I had those in my fridge.
No garlic in either of them?
None. My recipe is different.
-No garlic?
-No garlic.
I can mash it with my hand,
but the blender causes heat
and brings out the sourness
-from the olives.
-I see.
Also, originally…
I'm sorry, but do you know
that you only have 15 minutes?
CAN YOU TALK AND COOK?
Why is he out of breath?
-You're mostly just talking.
-Basil pesto is made with pine nuts…
-He must share his story.
-…but there were none.
Avocado also has lots of fat,
just like pine nuts, so I'll use that.
Both pine nuts and avocados
are rich in fat.
The avocado will act like pine nuts.
Like pine nuts.
So use avocado
to give it a texture like pine nuts.
ONION
GREEN ONION
CHEONGYANG PEPPER
2. MAKE SAUCE WITH ONION, GREEN ONION,
SOY SAUCE, PEPPER, RED PEPPER POWDER
AND ADD A KICK!
He's using parsley.
-Parsley.
-He's using parsley too.
Even the stems?
-He's using lots of parsley.
-He is.
OLIVE OIL
I had bought lots of parsley
to make lemon pasta.
I'm glad I did.
BUT…
Are you using both parsley and cilantro?
-Chef Sam!
-Yes?
No, I'm only using cilantro.
-It's not parsley.
-That's cilantro?
-It's cilantro?
-If we get something wrong, tell us so.
WE WERE GOING ON ABOUT PARSLEY…
I didn't know you were asking me.
You're not listening
to anything we're saying.
Don't just tell the story.
Listen a little too.
-The story almost got distorted.
-Exactly.
He's using cilantro now.
He made rice to make the burrito.
Sam, telling a story
begins by listening to others' stories.
TALKATIVE VERSUS QUIET
Sure.
He's cooking meat with green onion.
And a load of sugar!
-It's for the fried rice.
-That much sugar?
-Have you seen him use that much sugar?
-Chef Sam is using sugar?
I thought you were making kimchi jam!
-Chef Sam.
-Charlo liked it this way.
Okay. Sure.
All right.
-That's how Charlo liked it.
-I mean, he liked it.
-If he didn't, he wouldn't do that.
-You're right.
He's making it in a way that Charlo loved.
SALT
PEPPER
STIR-FRIED CILANTRO BRISKET
AS THE BURRITO FILLING
His basil pesto is done.
Is he going to mix the two?
Or use them separately?
-He's making two different sauces.
-They're different sauces.
Maybe he's making three.
-What's that?
-Truffle oil spray.
-Truffle oil.
-I see.
Truffle oil comes in a spray?
-Truffle oil and soy sauce.
-Those two go well together.
-They do.
-They go well very nicely.
And he already knew that 21 years ago?
He's something.
Wait, I think this is a recent technique.
-Is this your old technique?
-Yes.
-Really?
The technique from 21 years ago.
CHERRY TOMATOES
4. MIX CHERRY TOMATOES WITH TOMATO SAUCE
COMPLETED 4 SAUCES
The salt flew backward.
MISS
THAT WAS THE MOMENT I DREAMT OF SEEING…
I'M SORRY, DAE-MYUNG!
LET ME DO IT OVER!
MISS
Nothing got in.
I think he seasoned the kimchi fried rice.
Make sure you taste the fried rice.
He seasoned that instead.
4. COOK KIMCHI AND BEEF WITH RICE
He's even adding kimchi juice!
Where did you get kimchi from back then?
There was a Korean supermarket,
so I bought it there.
So there was a way to get them.
SHRIMP
-What's that?
-What are you doing, Chef Hyun-suk?
He's putting a stick into a shrimp
to keep it straight while it cooks.
-To make sure it doesn't bend.
-Vertically?
That's how we cook shrimp for sushi.
-Webfoot octopus.
-Even webfoot octopus?
When I just started my culinary school,
I often went to his restaurant,
and he always had the craziest dishes.
He did.
There was tsuyu dip pasta,
sushi-shaped pasta,
-also,
-Sushi-shaped?
…he tried matching caviar, bitter lettuce,
mukeunji, and other unusual mixes.
He used to make lots of creative pasta.
He must've been full of passion
when he first opened his business
as the head chef.
He did his best, but all he got was,
"He's doing the same thing
as he did at La Cucina."
"It's good, but it's just La Cucina."
That must've killed his pride.
-This is a significant dish for him.
-It is.
-He's grabbing yogurt.
-Yes.
And he uses it to…
-Yogurt?
-For the burrito.
-It's the sauce.
-The burrito sauce?
AH-HA
The dipping sauce.
Chef Jong-won also made
a similar yogurt sauce earlier.
Did they know the same person?
Were they the same person?
-No, his friend was called José.
-Wait.
Sanchez did mention
a friend named Martinez,
-and I heard he had a Korean friend.
-Hey!
Hey! Why have you changed?
ENTERTAINED
And that Korean friend
made a mean kimchi fried rice.
Hey, that's totally him!
THE PUZZLE HAS BEEN SOLVED!
GETTING CHILLS!
He said, "Hui-tae, Hui-tae,"
and I didn't know what it was.
-That's his Korean name!
-It was Chef Sam.
Why has he changed?
You two had a mutual friend.
SNAPS BACK TO REALITY
These tales literally never end.
I love it
when the chefs jab at each other.
CAN YOU STOP ME?
-He's making a burrito.
-He is.
NEXT, THE SIDE SALSA
Lemon juice.
Olive oil.
There's not much time left.
AVOCADO
I'm glad I had ripe avocados.
6. MIX WITH LEMON JUICE
AND MAKE TOMATO AVOCADO SALSA
CHECKING THE CAPELLINI
Oh, this capellini is too thick.
How long
do you usually cook capellini for?
About three or four minutes.
It only took two minutes
for the one I used.
These are quite thick.
-I see. Seven minutes left.
-All right.
You're halfway done.
Will you wash it in cold water?
-I have to.
-You do? Then leave it…
I said that it was cold capellini.
Why weren't you listening?
DUMBFOUNDED
-My gosh.
-He's scary.
That grandpa is scary when he's mad.
-He can be.
-I can't remember everything I hear.
He'll have to cook it longer
because it'll get firmer in cold water.
-Is that so?
-Yes.
He sprinkled it on his head.
TIME TO COOK THE MEAT!
DROPPING THE CILANTRO SIRLOIN MIX!
His kimchi fried rice is almost done.
You have less than six minutes.
7. ADD CILANTRO TO KIMCHI FRIED RICE
Is that cilantro?
Charlo liked cilantro,
-so I added a lot for him.
-Cilantro?
-You've added cilantro? That's new.
-That's new.
Did Charlo like that?
He did.
I think Dae-myung will like it more.
-Right.
-Not Charlo.
I think you're leaning toward
something Dae-myung would like.
-The lamb hambagu had cilantro in it too.
-It did!
You liked it with so much cilantro.
It felt like the cilantro
caught the lamb as it tried to run off.
-I think it'll taste like that.
-That story is so suspicious.
Is Charlo a real person?
-He is a real person!
-Is he really?
-He is.
-When I eat,
-can I talk to him on the phone?
-Phone?
-He wants to talk to him on the phone.
-Can you call him?
-I can.
-If you can, make it a video call.
-Five minutes.
-Five minutes left!
Please report from the kitchen, Jung-hwan.
Which one of their stories
will end up capturing his heart?
Does his friend actually exist?
Burrata! He's using burrata!
Rrata, rrata, burrata.
-Burrata!
-Rrata, rrata, burrata!
AND HE GRABS BEEF
What's he doing?
-Cutting meat.
-Meat? Now?
He must be using tenderloin.
Is he making beef tartare?
Ah-ha.
Other ingredients are used as toppings.
-Right.
-I see.
He has a piece of raw beef,
shrimp, and even apples.
-It's like sushi.
-Right.
-Jung-hwan, try the fried rice.
-I see kimchi fried rice.
Would it be any different?
It's how Charlo liked it,
made with cilantro.
-Let's see if he would've liked it.
-Fried rice for Charlo.
I should try it with the cilantro, right?
A BITE WITH A PIECE OF CILANTRO
It was over 20 years ago.
Kimchi fried rice.
-Does it taste like his memories?
-Does it taste star-obsessive?
Does it taste star-obsessive?
Huh?
It does taste star-obsessive.
I didn't know cilantro
would go so well with kimchi fried rice.
Really?
-It doesn't taste weird?
-I think they'd go well.
I see.
Come on, guys.
I'm talking about my actual friend.
-All right.
-I feel falsely framed.
But still,
-his story sounded a bit made up.
-It wasn't!
He's just making something delicious.
It has a unique flavor from cilantro.
-It's unique.
-It is? 3 minutes and 40 seconds.
CAPELLINI IS DONE
-It's out.
-Capellini is out.
That was the first cold pasta he made,
Chef Hyun-suk's cold capellini.
I'm sorry to say this,
-but I think Hyun-suk is over.
-Why?
He sprinkled salt on his head.
GETTING A HEADACHE
I guess it dropped on his head.
This is too sad.
He did this,
then his hand felt weak,
so he just let go.
OH, NO!
After doing this?
I see lots of salt on his head.
-Wasn't it dandruff?
-No, it's salt.
That's sadder than dandruff.
-He rarely tastes his dish more than once.
-Right.
-But he does it twice, three times now.
-He keeps tasting his food.
YOU MUST FEEL FULL
A little taste.
-He tastes it some more.
-He needs more pasta.
-It must've been salty.
-It's too salty.
-It must be salty.
-It's salty!
Salty, salty
WHY DOES HE KEEP TASTING HIS FOOD?
I guess they're all different.
They're all seasoned differently.
I guess so. That green sauce.
Two minutes and thirty seconds.
-Try that one.
-Hurry up!
-Let me try a strand of this.
-Right now.
What's important is
whether it's too salty.
He's one of the pioneers
of cold pasta in Korea,
someone who popularized it.
Is that right?
He did popularize it!
Yes, he did!
It's not too salty.
-The pioneer of cold pasta.
-That's him.
That's our grandpa.
He's the one who popularized it.
-Yes.
-The one who popularized cold pasta.
He's still that old Choi Hyun-suk.
-The pioneer.
-He's plating the dish now.
SAM MAKES HIS BURRITO
KIMCHI FRIED RICE,
CILANTRO SIRLOIN STIR-FRY
RIP!
9. WRAP BURRITO WITH YOGURT, RICE,
SIRLOIN, AND MORE CILANTRO
He's wrapping the burrito.
-Did you cut it?
-Yes.
-The burrito.
-With kimchi fried rice, right?
-It's all mixed inside?
-Yes.
Pioneer Choi, you need to start plating.
You don't have much time.
-Pioneer Choi!
-Pioneer Choi.
Wait, why are you
sticking out your bottoms like this?
RATHER SLOUCHY…
It's because his back hurts.
You had a great posture 21 years ago.
One minute.
He can't even see as well anymore.
-Like sushi.
-On top of it?
Sushi pasta.
Every single pasta is made with care.
MIX WELL TO FINISH
Sam finishes!
SAM KIM FINISHES
He finished with a minute left.
I'd like to share a story about my friend.
LAUGHING
He really is my friend,
and I finished early to explain.
He really loved it
whenever I made this for him.
-Forty seconds.
-Forty seconds. You have enough time.
On top of the cold pasta…
-It's all different.
-Four different flavors.
-Seafood and…
-He topped it with matching garnish.
He made 4 flavors in 15 minutes.
-Burrata.
-He made four different flavors?
-He also seasoned the pastas differently.
-He did.
Sam serves four burrito pieces,
and Hyun-suk serves four different pastas.
Four different ones?
Are you topping this with raw meat?
-It's raw? Ten. Nine.
-Right. A torch.
-Eight. Seven. Six.
-Eight. Seven.
BROILS THE TENDERLOIN!
Three. Two. One.
Time's up!
-Hyun-suk finishes too.
-Chef Hyun-suk's done too.
His cold capellini.
Now that we know the backstories,
these dishes look even better.
Wait, the presentation…
He did that on purpose
to make it seem like the old times.
Yes, like the old days.
It would be weird
if he served this without a story.
-It's more like my dish.
-Yes.
Yes, it's exactly like
what we had back then.
-Like those times.
-Yes.
Both dishes were finished for Dae-myung.
First, try the kimchi fried rice burrito
Sam made, thinking of Charlo.
YOGURT SAUCE
TOMATO AVOCADO SALSA
KIMCHI FRIED RICE BURRITO
THAT HOLDS MEMORIES WITH CHARLO
CHEF SAM KIM'S TAILS OF MEXICAN TALES
How should I eat it?
Grab a piece,
top it with some tomato and avocado salsa,
-and add sauce, then eat it in one bite.
-Okay.
It looks so good.
Did Charlo eat it like that?
I told him to eat it like that.
It's just like how Charlo ate it.
One second.
-What's up?
-The passport.
-I still have it.
-There's his passport again.
-My gosh.
-He couldn't enter Mexico before.
-I might end up going to America now.
-Right.
Can it bring him back to 2002?
I think he likes to show off his passport.
PFFT
Like, "I've traveled a lot."
I think the kimchi fried rice
would stand out.
I think they'll go well.
This is new.
It doesn't taste like
a mix of two different dishes,
but a single dish
that has always been like this.
-As if that's an actual dish?
-As if that's the case.
It's probably the cilantro.
My Mexican friends
all loved cilantro a lot,
and kimchi fried rice
can be too sour for them.
But they enjoyed it when I made this
with cilantro and avocados.
PERFECT FOR MEXICANS
When I think back on the time
he made this,
they were
two foreign nationals in America,
working hard to achieve their dreams.
My gosh.
-They must've had many ups and downs.
-While supporting each other.
He put the two dishes
they would've craved the most into one.
You're right.
It's an epic.
-It's a union of Korea and Mexico.
-It is.
-Korea-Mexico.
And in the center of that is the hero
of the 2002 World Cup, Jung-hwan.
He's the guy!
That's how the story gets tied together.
-We're all in this universe.
-You're right.
In a way, I made Sam.
It was you. You made him.
His tale continues to grow,
the tails of his tale.
When you listen to other people's stories,
you're ultimately a part of it too.
-Hey, Poong.
-Yes?
Your bangs are getting too curly.
-Your bangs are getting too curly.
-They are?
He's exhausted.
-I think it might rain tomorrow.
-Rain?
LOOKS IT UP
You're giving Sanchez vibes.
-It will rain tomorrow.
-I told you.
It'll rain tomorrow.
WEATHER FORECASTING BANGS
In 2002,
-I was near the City Hall.
-You were there?
Yes, there was a huge crowd,
-climbing up on the bus and all.
-Yes, people did that.
But I was a third-time exam repeater.
You're a third-timer?
I did too!
I repeated the college exam five times.
APOLOGIZES IMMEDIATELY
Five times?
And back then, I was greatly encouraged.
-I'm glad.
-I'm sure
-it was the same for Sam and his friend.
-You're right.
I spent the night up cheering for Korea
at a Korean supermarket.
You gathered at a Korean supermarket?
-And Charlo came with you?
-Yes, he joined me to root for Korea.
-Gosh.
It's such a heartfelt story.
He just cried.
Dae-myung wipes his tears off.
Chef Hyun-suk doesn't look so pleased.
FULL OF WORRIES
The cold pasta.
Why didn't you finish first?
MARGHERITA CAPELLINI
BASIL PESTO CAPELLINI
OLIVE ANCHOVY CAPELLINI
TRUFFLE SOY SAUCE CAPELLINI
CHEF CHOI HYUN-SUK'S
ANNALS OF THE CHOI HYUN-SUK DYNASTY
The order of the pasta isn't random.
They're in the order of creation.
He had a reason there too?
-There's a story.
-Yes.
Start from the left and go right.
-The meat pasta is the last one?
-It is.
-This is his life on a plate.
-Yes.
-Thank you.
It's the first page of his annals.
-Chapter one.
-He opened his own restaurant 21 years ago
after leaving La Cucina
and created this cold pasta.
WHAT'S HIS FIRST CAPELLINI LIKE?
Choi Hyun-suk.
-Chapter one.
CHAPTER 1 OF THE ANNALS
How can I put this?
It tastes very adamant.
-Adamant?
It's both sour yet creamy.
Quite youthful and passionate.
Back then,
my teacher didn't like it
when we tampered with the recipe.
He thought adding new ideas
would make the dish a joke,
-so I made it and served it in secret.
-In secret?
-It's a simple tomato and basil pasta.
-The essence of his youth.
-The flavor of youth.
-That vigor.
But he's not allowed to do that, is he?
-He can't.
-He would've been berated.
There was a chef's special on the menu
that changed every day,
so I took my freedom with that.
-When his heart burned with passion.
-Yes.
After that, I began to take
that creative journey.
And now, chapter two.
Chapter two, cold basil pesto capellini.
-Chapter two, basil pesto.
-This is where the journey began.
He opened up his epoch with this one.
Chapter two.
It's shocking.
-Shocking?
-Crazy.
I can sense the shock
when a pasta like this first came out.
Can you feel it?
-Basil pesto wasn't well known back then.
-That's true.
I tried making basil pesto pasta at home,
but I've never had anything like this.
It's not easy to do.
And Hyun-suk was the one who made it.
He's getting emotional.
MASTER CHOI!
Why is he low-key annoying?
He remembers the pain and agony.
-Did he poke his eyes?
-It's all coming back.
HIS WHITES TURNED RED
-Now, chapter three.
-Year 2015.
-Cold anchovy capellini.
-Chapter three means…
The beginning of Chef & My Fridge.
10 YEARS AGO,
BACK WHEN HE OWNED THE SHOW…
That was the era
when I became overly ambitious
and made many intense dishes.
Grandpa Choi Hyun-suk
with broken tear ducts.
-Cold anchovy capellini.
-And webfoot octopus.
What's chapter three like?
-Does he show himself?
-His own colors.
When people don't know much about food,
they think everything cooked
with olive oil tastes like this.
They have no idea
it's made with anchovies.
It shows that
he has a strong card to play.
-I see.
-Anchovies.
Who would've thought to mix
olive oil with anchovies?
-An Italian man.
-What?
SON JONG-WON, YOU!
He's also doing his best.
-Let's show him support.
-Yes.
-The last chapter. Truffle oil capellini.
-The last chapter.
So this is him now, right?
-The grandpa.
-The grandpa pasta.
It was when I tried using
many different ingredients.
When he made new attempts.
That was when he was in his prime.
The last chapter is important.
-There is this young man.
-He mentions a young man.
He meets a great person, gets married,
and does his best at work
to provide for his family.
Now, he has a baby to take care of.
He continues to live diligently,
and his girl grows up too.
AMAZED
-And then, his daughter gets married.
-Oh, right.
Soon, she also has a child of her own,
a grandson who looks just like him.
This was a dish that showcased
the ups and downs of a man's life,
and I can call this The Husband.
-Wow.
-The Husband?
Hey, you tied that in at the end?
THE REVIEWER
THIS IS THE STORY OF MY JOURNEY
TO BECOME THE BEST CHEF
I had forgotten for a moment.
So you should have some pasta
on Saturday, July 4th.
EVEN TIES HIS DRAMA INTO THIS
Then on Sunday, watch Chef & My Fridge
to make your weekend perfect.
You have to choose one of the two chefs.
Press one to choose Sam,
and two to choose Hyun-suk.
Please press the button!
-Okay.
-He pressed it.
They're only one star apart right now.
Which story did he choose?
Let's see the result.
Show us!
Food, Vibe, Chefs.
The story is as important as the food.
Chef Hyun-suk versus Chef Sam.
Will it be Choi Hyun-suk,
who made cold capellini
when he first opened
his own establishment?
Or Sam Kim, who made
kimchi fried rice burritos
for his Mexican friend, Charlo?
Kim Dae-myung's choice!
Which story touched him deeper?
Who's the winner?
Who's the winner? The winner…
CHOI HYUN-SUK WINS
Choi Hyun-suk wins!
ANNALS OF CHOI HYUN-SUK DYNASTY WINS
Chef Hyun-suk wins!
The man who popularized cold pasta
twenty-one years ago has won.
Both stories were very touching,
but Chef Sam's story reminded me
of a passionate young man's book
that was yet to be finished.
But as for Chef Hyun-suk,
he has written about his life
almost until the very end
-and he's now looking back on it.
-It wasn't that far.
It's not like he'll pass away soon.
He's healthy and well.
This was his first season,
and the second one will follow.
It felt like the end of the first season,
as if I have read a long epic.
It was so moving. And I mean it.
I see.
This means
he managed to end the losing streak
against Sam after the fourth loss…
-It's done.
-…through this round.
They also have
the same number of stars now.
Let's hear from him.
I rarely look back on past recipes
or serve them again to a guest.
As I looked at the very first dish I made,
I got a chance
to look back at where I started.
It must be a nice opportunity.
Chef Sam.
Cooking is all about why you started.
Don't forget that.
ALLERGIC TO CHEESY QUOTES
A piece of advice from a grandpa.
And you. Stay behind.
I have to go home ASAP.
Sam, you should say hi to Charlo.
To keep it short,
Charlo.
Te extraño.
It means, "I miss you."
-"I miss you."
-It means that I miss him.
Chef Hyun-suk rises as the winner today.
-Please put a star on him!
-Congratulations.
Hyun-suk finally beats Sam
and wins his sixth star
-from Kim Dae-myung!
-Thank you.
COMING UP: PREVIEW FOR
KARINA & WINTER'S EPISODE
Today's fridge owners are
KARINA and WINTER of aespa!
I plan to go very far today.
I hope our episodes are the funniest.
AN EXTRAORDINARY DETERMINATION
I can rotate my arm all the way.
SHOWING OFF ALL THEIR PARTY TRICKS
SEAL CLAP
CAN'T BELIEVE AESPA IS GOING THIS FAR
AESPA CAME PREPARED TODAY,
SO THE CHEFS ARE PREPARED TOO
WHOA
It'd be nice
if someone could grate the cheese.
AS ALWAYS, CHEF SOMEONE IS SUMMONED
He doesn't look happy!
I trusted him far too much.
-Oh, no.
-You trusted him too much.
I think Sam got you.
A METALLIC-FLAVORED DISH FOR AESPA
STARTING WITH THE KNIFE-FLAVOR
TO THE FIERY FLAVOR
A FEAST OF MANY FLAVORS
-It's an emergency.
-It's not.
Stop acting up.
EVEN HER WORDS ARE METALLIC
KARINA DOES THE 5-MINUTE CHECK
It's delicious!
HER SEAL CLAPPING NEVER ENDS
BUT WHAT DOES IT TASTE LIKE?
I'm sorry, but tell us
instead of sending signals.
WHO'LL BECOME AESPA'S FAVORITE CHEF?
-Ho-young's pretty much an actual seal.
-Wow.
Subtitle translation by: Eunsook Youn